http://www.bootbay.com/wcs/shop/en/bootbay/privacy-policy-bootbay

Message Dialog
Close
Display Update Message
Product Comparison
The maximum number of products that can be compared is 4. Please refine your selection.
OK
Your session is about to timeout due to inactivity.
Click OK to extend your time for an additional 30 minutes.
OK
This item has been successfully added to your favorites.
0
This item has been successfully added:
We respect your privacy
We want to assure you that your personal information is safe with us at BootBay.com. Certain actions on our website require us to collect personally-identifying information that is necessary to process purchase transactions. BootBay.com will not rent, sell, or distribute potentially personal information to any outside sources. BootBay.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of BootBay.com, third parties or the public at large. BootBay.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. BootBay.com will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.
What is a "COOKIE"?
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Without cookies, BootBay.com can't keep track of the items you've placed in your cart or perform other crucial e-commerce capabilities. We do not use cookies to intrude in your privacy or do anything other than match you up with your information on our site.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor and infrequent, BootBay.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
QUESTIONS?
We'll be happy to provide additional information or answer any questions.
Please email your questions/comments to info@bootbay.com. Or call us 800.930.3668.
